<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FF Emotes - Dances, Skins</string>
    <string name="dia_guide">Learn how to win gold and diamonds\n\n In Free Fire you don\'t just want to win, you want to show off unique weapon skins and features. To do this, you need to accumulate gold and diamonds by playing or paying with real money. Due to the amount of options, events and menus, many of us may feel confused.\n\n Discover the methods of winning gold and diamonds, and how to spend them to unlock various items in the game. We have compiled the 5 ways to win gold and diamonds, supported by images to help you in the best possible way.\n\nPlay Games\n\n We will get a sum of gold just for participating, so entering a game will always be a good time invested. If you want to earn more money, it\'s good to practice and work hard, as the game rewards survival time, final position, eliminations and headshots. In addition, by playing games you will be able to complete daily challenges.\n\n There are a variety of different challenges, especially if you have purchased Elite Pass (only unlocked with real money). When you complete a challenge, you\'ll receive one or more explosive medals. The tasks are usually to play a certain number of minutes, use specific weapons, reach a specific number of eliminations or end up in high positions.\n\n Explosive medals are used for the Fire Pass. On this site, you\'ll unlock items as you get more medals. If you purchase Elite Pass, you\'ll get better rewards in the form of gold, diamonds and even skins. Otherwise, you can limit yourself to the Free Pass, but the rewards will be much scarcer.\n\nEnter the game every day\n\n This is a simple and safe way to earn gold, but in no case will we get diamonds just for entering. The daily rewards always come out when you enter the game and, as a general rule, you will get 350 gold each week. It\'s a very easy way to accumulate this virtual money, so try to get into Free Fire every day.\n\n Open free boxes and participate in Gold Royale\n\n Every day we\'ll have a free box in the game store. To find this box, go to the Normal section and click on the Offer of the day section.\n\n There is also the famous Luck Royale, which we can access from the main menu. There we test our luck. However, you can participate in Gold Royale with so-called normal vouchers or by spending gold. If we only use normal vouchers for Gold Royale, the first two rewards for weekly spins usually contain 100 gold coins each. To purchase these rewards, click on the red colored bags to the right of Gold Royale.\n\n Finally, you\'ll sometimes get Lucky Draw, which is just an extra prize the game awards at random. Press one of the three cards and you\'ll get another reward with minimal effort. It usually gives little gold, and it\'s also possible to get memory fragments, among other items.</string>
    <string name="tips_tricks">Become the best with these tips\n\n In Free Fire we have many tools at our disposal to become the last survivor standing, but you must also know how to use them. Discover how to become the best Free Fire player with these tips.\n\nChoose the right landing site\n\n Choosing the landing site is only the first step to victory. Although it may seem trivial, it\'s not; determining where you\'ll start will allow you to decide whether to start the game right or not. It\'s important to choose a place isolated from other players, near a city but not so close to it.\n\n Therefore, the best option is to fall out of towns and cities, observe where others fall and then enter to explore. It is fundamental not to expose ourselves too much until we are properly equipped, especially when we move around places with loot in quantity and quality, where many times there will be players.\n\nGet equipment\n\n As soon as we land, the first thing we have to do is to find weapons, protection, first aid kits, among other things. At the beginning of the game, the best thing to do is to grab everything we can find, as we can always improve and change the equipment.\n\nExplore military sites\n\n If there are no enemies in sight, it\'s a good idea to explore sites like watchtowers, cargo containers, trenches or military tents. There are usually good loot in these kinds of places, both in weaponry and supplies.\n\n It\'s not very smart to explore these areas from the beginning, but if we\'re halfway through the game, there will always be things to take. Surely there will be fewer players lurking around to eliminate us.\n\n In places like this, it\'s also common to find kits to improve bulletproof vests. Pay attention as you explore because, although it\'s okay to have a level one vest, it\'s highly recommended to upgrade it soon. The last players will always have a powerful weapon.\n\nPay attention to the safe are\n\n The safe zone is described by a white circle, which we can see both on the map and in the mini-map. Inside this zone we will be safe, since, outside of it, the radioactive storm will take away our life with the passage of time.\n\n If we pay attention to the safe area, we will often see players running for their lives to get away from the storm, before it\'s too late. Situations like this are a perfect opportunity to eliminate opponents.\n\nLook at the mini-map\n\n The mini-map is very important to avoid a whole series of threats to our survival\n\n If you hear gunshots close to you, look for the red triangles in the mini-map, as they will indicate the origin of the shots. This way you will know where there are enemies nearby. At other times, we\'ll hear explosions and vehicles driven by players. Both will be marked by yellow or red dots around the mini-map. That will tell us which direction the sound is coming from.\n\n In addition to radiation, there are also danger zones. These zones are marked by red circles with the label Danger. After a few seconds, a bomber will destroy that place, so get away as soon as possible! UAV drones reveal the position of players within the yellow circle. Never expose yourself to others, but stay close to see where the revealed players are.\n\nTake cover\n\n All over the map there are buildings, walls, containers, stones, trees, etc. Use them as cover! The worst thing we can do in this game is be exposed. While you\'re on the move, try to protect yourself with the environment so that you don\'t fall out of the way in the face of observant players.\n\n However, that means we have to move carefully. We\'ll never know if behind that wall, or that wall of the building, hides an opponent with a shotgun, ready to get us out of the game with two surprise shots.\n\nUse vehicles with care\n\n The vehicles are used to move quickly to other places, where there is quality loot, and also to pass over the absent-minded players that we find on the road.\n\n If we make too much noise, the other players will be able to hear us. For that reason, use cars, vans and motorcycles carefully, so as not to reveal our position.</string>
    <string name="download_des_1">Some skins or weapon require Costume Collection pack. Please download the full Costume Collection pack (around 900mb or more) for the best experience.\n\n If the first application of the skin weapon fails, please restart FF and reapply the skin pack.\n\n The mod may expire if FF updates the new version, if mod does not work please open the app deactivate and re-activate the skin. We will continuously update to bring the best packages for you.</string>

</resources>